#### Glarysoft Privacy Policy

##### Effective Date: May 29, 2018

Glarysoft Ltd. (''Glarysoft'') is committed to preserving the privacy of our users. We know how much you care about the way your Personal Data is used. In that regard, we have established for the Sites and/or Services the following privacy policy to explain and describe what personal information Glarysoft collects on our Sites and/or Services, how Glarysoft uses it and your options regarding information Glarysoft may collect about you. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this Policy. This Privacy Policy is a part of and incorporated into Glarysoft's Terms of Use and End User License Agreements associated with its Sites and/or Services.  
  
Please read the Glarysoft Online Privacy Statement below to know about the particular information we may collect.  
  
If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to [\[email protected\]](https://www.glarysoft.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).  

##### 1\. Information We Collect

In describing our collection, use, and sharing of information in this Policy, we refer to our collection and use of "Personal Information." "Personal Information," as used in this Policy, is personally identifiable information, which is information that directly identifies an individual, such as first and last name, mailing address, email address, billing information, IP addresses, demographics, passwords or other online contact information, or telephone number. We collect Personal Information, as well as non-personally identifiable information on Glarysoft Sites and/or Services.  
  
We collect Personal Information in two ways. First, we collect information you provide to us in optional, voluntary submissions, such as in registration forms, user profiles, promotional signups, sweepstakes/contest entries, requests for customer service, software and mobile applications downloads and curriculum vitae submissions. Second, some Personal Information may be collected automatically.  
  
We may also obtain information, including Personal Information, from third-party sources. If we directly combine information from third-party with Personal Information that we have collected, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information and handle it in accordance with this Policy. In addition, please note that we may solicit third-party to collect Personal Information on our behalf and in such cases we instruct those third-party to comply with this Policy and all applicable data protection laws.  
  
Please be aware that we are prohibited from conditioning a child's participation in any activity on that child disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in that activity. You are under no obligation to provide and can decline to provide, any requested information at any time. However, if you decline to provide personal information that is reasonably necessary to participate in certain activities, you may not be able to participate in those activities on certain Sites and/or Services.  
  
We may receive information through a variety of methods including but not limited to:  

##### Accessing and Modifying Your Personal Information

Submitting Personal Information  
  
If you do not want to submit Personal Information that is necessary to provide or use our Sites and/or Services or to fulfill your request, you will not be able to access and/or participate in certain Glarysoft Sites and/or Services. For example, you will not be able to register for an account with us or participate in certain contests or promotions, or access and/or use certain Glarysoft product features or online services. In addition, your refusal to submit Personal Information may limit our ability to respond to your customer support inquiry in a timely fashion.  
  
Editing Personal Information  
  
You may, at any time, update, correct, or delete certain Personal Information that you have provided to us by updating your preferences on the Account Settings page or by contacting us at the mailing or email address set forth in this Policy.  
  
Marketing Choices  
  
If you want to remove yourself from individual communications, including marketing promotions, advertisements, updates and email newsletters, simply click the unsubscribe link in the communication or access your Account Settings page when logged in. You also acknowledge and agree that there may be instances where we may elect to notify you about administrative notices regarding your account with us, such as to inform you about changes to our terms, conditions, and policies, that your account may be expiring, or to provide you with other relevant administrative information about your account. Because this information is important to your interaction with us, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.  
  
Account Deletion  
  
If you submit Personal Information, you may delete your account with us at any time. If you delete your account, your Personal Information and any and all other accounts related information including, but not limited to, user profile data, sharing data and any other data, credits specifically associated with your account are also permanently deleted. If you choose to have an account with us in the future, you will have to sign up for a new account as none of the information you previously provided or saved within your account will have been saved.  
  
Access to Personal Information  
  
You may view, correct, amend, or delete the Personal Information Glarysoft stores about you where it is inaccurate or if you believe the Personal Information has been processed contrary to the terms of this Policy except to the extent where the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to your privacy in the case in question or where the rights of persons other than yours would be violated. Most of your Personal Information may be accessed and corrected by simply logging into your account and accessing your profile. If you wish to obtain a report of the Personal Information Glarysoft has about you, please send us a written request at the address set forth in this Policy.  

##### Cookies

"Cookies" are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently. Glarysoft and its marketing partners or suppliers may use cookies or other technologies when you interact with the website or use the products. By using our site, you agree to the use of cookies as described in this privacy policy.  
  
To improve our site, we use cookies to save our users' usernames and passwords so that they don't have to re-enter them each time they visit the Glarysoft site. We might also use cookies in the Software to allow us to track from which vendor users purchased Glarysoft.  
  
Glarysoft does not require that you accept cookies and/or you may withdraw your consent to our use of cookies at any time by adjusting your browser's privacy settings, however, some functionality on our Sites (e.g. "functionality cookies"), our product or service check-out process, and Services may be disabled if you decline to accept cookies ( e.g. "necessary cookies").  
  
By using the Sites and Services, you consent to the placement of the cookies referenced above. You can, however, set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. You may also change your cookie settings through preference options in our Sites and/or Services, where applicable. We will indicate that upon selecting your preferences, that we will use a cookie to remember your preferences.  
  
Glarysoft never gives away information about our users. If you choose to provide Personal Information about yourself, Glarysoft will use this information only to communicate directly with you. Glarysoft will not sell, rent or otherwise disclose that information to third-party unless such disclosure is necessary for the purposes set forth in this Policy, by law or a policy or notice contained or associated with a specific Site(s) and/or Service(s).  

##### Third-party Advertising Technologies and Social Networks

In addition to using cookies and related technologies as described above, we also may permit certain third-party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to users and to collect and use other data about user activities on our Sites and/or Services (e.g., to allow them to tailor ads on third-party services). These companies may deliver ads that might also place cookies and otherwise track user behavior. These companies may use information about user behavior in order to provide customized advertisements across various services and products. In the course of providing these services, products or placing advertisements, these third-party companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer and may record information to these cookies based upon your activities on any of our Sites and/or Services and on third-party websites. Each of these companies uses this cookie information according to their own privacy and security policies. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out as indicated in this Policy. Please note this does not opt you out of being delivered advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.  
  
If you choose to 'share' Glarysoft products with friends through Facebook, Twitter or other social networks, you might be sent cookies from these websites. We don't control the setting of these cookies, so please check those websites for more information about their cookies and how to manage them.  

##### Analytics Tools

We use analytics tools and other third-party technologies, such as Google Analytics and DoubleClick Cookies, to collect non-personal information in the form of various usage and user metrics when you use our online Sites and/or Services. These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including cookies, IP addresses, device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, onsite behavior and usage information, feature use metrics and statistics, usage and purchase history, MAC Address, mobile unique device ID, and other similar information.  
  
The third-party analytics companies who collect information on our Sites and/or Services and other online products and/or services may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online or mobile products and services relating to your activities across their network of websites as well as online and/or mobile products and services. Many of these companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies.  
  
You may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).  

##### Feedback

There are many opportunities to contact us via our website. There are links that allow you to reach us by email, by signing up our Affiliate Program or by requesting online support. If you choose to sign up our Affiliate Program, you are asked to provide us with your name, email address, your website, your physical address and ZIP code. If you contact us by submitting an online support request, you may also need to provide us with your computer details by running our tool for further investigating the issue you encountered.  

##### Log files

When you visit our website, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends. These log files tell us generally about the visitors to our site - general geographic regions, length of visits, pages clicked on, and so forth. We can't tell who you are by examining our log files, except as anonymous users.  

##### Device Information

We may collect information about the device you are using, our products and services or, including what type of device it is, what operating systems you are using, device settings, application IDs, unique device identifiers, and crash data. We use device identifiers to analyze our traffic.  

##### Product Use Information

Some of our products allow us to gather information about your computer (including your IP address), other software you use, and about what features you use in our software. This is common for many software products, including games, AntiVirus, and office tools. This information is always completely anonymous and only ever used to better understand how people use our software and how we can improve our products.  
  
We may disclose your personal information to third-party if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our license terms or terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Glarysoft Software Limited, our customers, or others.  

##### Purchases

If you purchase one of our products, the payment will be handled by a 3rd party payment gateway. They will collect information about you, such as your name and address and credit card details. They only share the minimum with us that we need to set up your account with Glarysoft. We do not receive any of your credit card details from a 3rd party payment gateway. If you opt in to receive marketing communications from us, they will share your name, email address and any other information you provide to them for this purpose.  
  
Cleverbridge have their own privacy policy which you can see at [http://www.cleverbridge.com/?scope=contact&id=9EihWvhAUN&progress=privacy](http://www.cleverbridge.com/?scope=contact&id=9EihWvhAUN&progress=privacy).  
  
Avangate have their own privacy policy which you can see at [http://www.avangate.com/privacy.php](http://www.avangate.com/privacy.php).  
  
MyCommerce have their own privacy policy which you can see at [https://www.mycommerce.com/corporate-policy/](https://www.mycommerce.com/corporate-policy/).  

##### Search

Some of the web search services provided herein are provided by Trovi Search and powered by Trovi search partners. For information on the web search services data collection, please visit http://info.trovi.com/Privacy, and the search provider's privacy policy, as applicable.  

##### Download

The Glarysoft website ("Glarysoft Website'') entitles our users to use Glarysoft software (the ''Software"), both online and after downloading it. To improve our site and as part of the registration process, after downloading the Software, Glarysoft requests the following information: the user's age range, gender, country, zip code, e-mail address and general interests. The purpose of gathering this information is to help Glarysoft provide better service to our users and aggregate information to third-party interested in usage patterns of different demographic groups. Glarysoft may share information about users with business partners, sponsors and other third-party; however, we do so only in the aggregate and never on a personal basis.  
  
The Glarysoft Website contains links to other sites from which the Software can be downloaded. Glarysoft does not share any information provided by our users with these sites. Additionally, Glarysoft is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.  

##### 2\. How We Use Information

Generally, we use Personal Information to establish and enhance our relationship with our users through four main categories: (1) Optimization; (2) Communication; and (3) Sharing Features. Below, we provide some specific examples of how we use the Personal Information and other information we collect.  

##### a. Optimization

Glarysoft collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve its sites and deliver the services or carry out the transactions you have requested. These uses may include providing you with more effective customer service; making the sites or services easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our Sites and Services, to develop new products and services; and displaying content and advertising that are customized to your interests and preferences.  

##### b. Communication and Responding to Requests

We use your information, including Personal Information to provide you with customer support, process transactions, respond to users' requests, send newsletters and updates, send special offers and advertisements, seek your opinions and feedback, and connect users to Glarysoft Sites and/or Services, and to products and services of our partners and licensees.  

##### c. Sharing Features

We use your information, including Personal Information and any other information you submit directly or through passive means to provide you with various ways to connect and share content (e.g., web content, user-generated videos, text, drawings, and screen and lecture captures, and quizzing features, media, tools, services and other products) with third-party. For example, we may provide you with the opportunity to email a link to certain content to another person. To use this feature, we may require you to provide certain Personal Information including your email address and the email address of each person to whom you send the link.  
  
We also may allow you to share links to content with users of various third-party services (e.g., social networking, search and sharing services). When sharing links using one of these third-party services, if you are not already logged in to the third-party service, you will need to supply login credentials for it. If you are not a registered user of the third-party service, you will need to sign up for it. You are supplying the registration information or login credentials for the third-party service directly to that third-party, and not to us. By using any of these third-party services to share links to content, you permit us to access, use and disclose any information relating to your account on each such third-party service (such as your username and profile information) that is available to us through the third-party service, including through its application programming interface (API) pursuant to this Policy.  
  
More Specifically, Glarysoft Sites and/or Services may use interfaces with social media sites such as Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter and others. If you choose to "like" or share information from the Glarysoft Sites and/or Services through these services, you should review the privacy policy of that service. If you are a member of a social media site, the interfaces may allow the social media site to connect your site visit to your personally identifiable information resulting in the public display of the same.  

##### 3\. How We Protect the Information We Collect

##### a. Safeguards for Personal Information

We take reasonable measures, including the implementation and maintenance of physical, electronic, and managerial procedures, in an effort to assure the security, integrity, and accuracy of all Personal Information that we collect. Our efforts include procedures designed to avoid unauthorized access, alteration, loss, misuse, disclosure, or destruction of Personal Information taking into account the risks involved in the processing and the nature of the Personal Information.  
  
If we learn of a security systems breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using the Glarysoft Sites and/or Services covered by this Policy and providing Personal Information to us, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your account information and usage.  
  
No one can guarantee, and we do not guarantee, that your personal information is completely secure at all time. You are also responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your personal information to protect it against unauthorized access or use. If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always choose to log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users.  
  
Personal information collected on Glarysoft sites and services may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Glarysoft or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using a Glarysoft site or service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Glarysoft abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.  

##### b. Spam and Sale of Information

We hate spam. We will never spam you with any unsolicited email, and we will never sell the information you have given us to other parties. Glarysoft will not sell, lease or rent its email subscriber lists to third-party. Using tools such as the Inbox Protector and being cautious about the sharing of your email address while online will help reduce the amount of unsolicited email you receive.  

##### 4\. Third-party Login Functionality

We may permit users with accounts on certain third-party services, including but not limited to, social networking, search, sharing, and other services delivered by third-parties, to bypass the standard applicable registration process. If you connect through an authorized third-party service, you will be able to use your third-party login information to log in to your Glarysoft account or access Glarysoft content, Sites and/or Services. We are not responsible for the sharing, posting, commenting, or other content and information gathering practices of any third-party services that may be triggered by using these third-party login services. Please review their terms of service and privacy policies carefully before using third-party login functionality to access any Glarysoft Sites and/or Services.  
  
By using any third-party services to log in to your Glarysoft account or access Glarysoft Sites and/or Services, you permit us to access, store and use all information related to your third-party account that may be accessible to us through the third-party service, including through its application programming interface (API), pursuant to this Policy.  

##### 5\. Third-party Services and Links

Glarysoft's content, including forums contests, products, services, newsletters and communications that we send to our users, may contain links to content provided by third-parties. For example, our communications may contain links to third-party merchants from whom you may purchase products. To purchase products from these third-party merchants, you may be required to provide Personal Information, including your credit card or other payment information.  

##### 6\. Children Under 16

We do not knowingly seek or collect Personal Information from users under the age of 16, except to the extent that Glarysoft may collect limited personal information from students (but not their email addresses), but only where that student's school or school district, has contracted with Glarysoft to collect the personal information from students for the educational context authorized by the school or school district. Children under 16 years old are not allowed to create an account without a parent's or guardian's express consent. We recommend that minors over the age of 16 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.  
  
We require schools or school districts to obtain parental or guardian consent from a student's parent or guardian before collecting any such student Personal Information. If you are a student, please do not send any Personal Information about yourself to us, other than what we request from you when you sign up for any of our Sites and/or Services. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a student without parental or guardian consent being obtained by his or her school or school district, or if we learn a student has provided us Personal Information beyond what we request when he or she signs up for any of our Sites and/or Services, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that a student may have provided us Personal Information beyond what is requested when signing up for any of our Sites and/or Services, or that a student's school or school district has not obtained parental or guardian consent, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.glarysoft.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).  
  
Notwithstanding anything to the contrary contained in this Policy, if you are a student as described above, and your parent or guardian signed up for our Sites and/or Service with a password or access ID provided by your school, you understand that your parent or guardian may be able to view all information within or associated with your account, including, without limitation, messages between you and your teacher and grades you received on your assignment.  

##### 7\. Notification in the event of a breach

In the unlikely event of a breach in the security of personal data, we will notify all users who are actually or potentially affected.  
  
We may tailor the method of notice depending on the circumstances. Where the only contact information that we have for you is an email address, then the notification will necessarily be by email. We may also elect to give you notice via our in-product messaging system. Where we believe there are affected users for which we have no contact information on file, we may give notice via publication on our company website.  
  
We reserve the right to delay notification if we are asked to do so by law enforcement or other authorities, or if we believe that giving notice immediately will increase the risk of harm to our user body overall.  

##### 8\. International Transfers of Your Personal Data

We are a global business that provides its products and services all around the world. In order to reach all of our users and provide all of them with our software, we operate on an infrastructure that spans the globe. The servers that are part of this infrastructure may therefore be located in a country different than the one where you live. Regardless, we provide the same GDPR-level of protection to all personal data it processes.  
  
At the same time, when we transfer personal data outside of the EEA, we always make sure to put in place appropriate and suitable safeguards, such as standardized contracts approved by the European Commission, which legally bind the receiving party to adhere to a high level of protection, and to ensure that your data remains safe and secure at all times and that your rights are protected.  
  
Situations where we transfer personal data outside of the EEA include the provision of our products and services, processing of transactions and your payment details, and the provision of support services.  

##### 9\. Data Protection Officer

To protect user data security, we have a Data Protection Officer (DPO) to monitor our protection of user data, provide advice as required and cooperate with regulatory agencies. You can contact our data protection officer at [\[email protected\]](https://www.glarysoft.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).  

##### 10\. Changes and Updates to This Policy

We may update this Policy from time to time. If we do, we will update the "effective date" at the top of the Policy. If we make material changes to how we use Personal Information, we will attempt to notify you of the change and to give you the opportunity to exercise choice as to how your Personal Information is used. We will post the updated Policy on the affected Sites and/or Service, and if we have your email address, we will send notice of the update to that email address.  
  
We encourage you to review this Policy periodically to stay informed about our collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information. Your continued use of our Sites and/or Services or any other content, products or other services covered by this Policy constitutes your agreement to this Policy and any updates.  

##### 11\. No Error Free Performance

Glarysoft does not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. Glarysoft will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action when Glarysoft learns of any failure to comply with our Privacy Policy. Glarysoft shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this Privacy Policy.  

##### 12\. Installation of Glarysoft Software

By installing Glarysoft software, you are agreeing to the Terms and Conditions contained in the EULA (end-user license agreement) that appears when you run the installation programs. Please refer to [https://www.glarysoft.com/inf/eula/](https://www.glarysoft.com/inf/eula/) for more information.  

##### 13\. Contact Us

Glarysoft regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or Glarysoft's treatment of personal information by contacting us through this website. If you have questions about this statement or believe that we have not adhered to it, please contact us.  
  
Email: [\[email protected\]](https://www.glarysoft.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
